<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<shared_knowledge>
  <report_agent>
1. The script initiated the report generation process, internally setting up dummy model performance data that includes classification summaries, model metadata, and overall metrics.
2. The script analyzed the internally provided dummy model execution results by formatting them into a comprehensive text report. This involved creating sections for chest X-ray classification summaries, model information (name, version, training date), and overall performance metrics (accuracy, precision, recall per condition).
3. The script stored the generated report by first ensuring the directory "report_agent" existed, and then writing the complete text report content to the file "report_agent/analysis_report.txt".
4. The report generation process was confirmed as complete.
</report_agent>
  <report>
1. The script started by indicating the initiation of report generation.
2. It defined a dictionary named `model_results` containing a list of classification predictions, each with a label and an associated probability, simulating output from a chest X-ray analysis model.
3. It converted these `model_results` predictions into a pandas DataFrame.
4. The DataFrame was then sorted in descending order based on the 'probability' column.
5. The top 5 predictions from the sorted DataFrame were selected.
6. A string variable `report_content` was initialized to hold the report's structure.
7. The script added a section to `report_content` detailing the top 5 classification results and their probabilities, iterating through the selected pandas DataFrame.
8. A dictionary named `interpretations` was defined, mapping various medical conditions to their brief explanatory texts.
9. Another section was added to `report_content` providing brief interpretations for each of the top 5 findings, by looking up their explanations in the `interpretations` dictionary.
10. A summary section was generated and added to `report_content`, highlighting the most probable condition and another significant finding, along with their probabilities.
11. A concluding statement regarding the importance of clinical correlation was appended to `report_content`.
12. It defined an output directory path as "workspace/report".
13. The script ensured that the output directory "workspace/report" existed by creating it if it didn't already.
14. Finally, the complete `report_content` string was saved as a text file named "analysis_report.txt" within the "workspace/report" directory.
15. A completion message was printed, indicating that report generation was complete.
</report>
</shared_knowledge>