<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<shared_knowledge>
  <report_agent>
1. The script initiated the report generation process, internally setting up dummy model performance data that includes classification summaries, model metadata, and overall metrics.
2. The script analyzed the internally provided dummy model execution results by formatting them into a comprehensive text report. This involved creating sections for chest X-ray classification summaries, model information (name, version, training date), and overall performance metrics (accuracy, precision, recall per condition).
3. The script stored the generated report by first ensuring the directory "report_agent" existed, and then writing the complete text report content to the file "report_agent/analysis_report.txt".
4. The report generation process was confirmed as complete.
</report_agent>
  <report>
1. The script initiated the generation of a Chest X-ray classification report.
2. It attempted to load model results from 'workspace/model_results.json' but the file was not found.
3. As a result of the missing file, dummy classification results were generated and used for the report, including a summary indicating dummy data usage, specific findings with probabilities (Atelectasis, Cardiomegaly, Pleural Effusion, Pneumonia, No Finding), and a dummy image ID.
4. Report content was prepared based on these dummy results, encompassing a report header with a timestamp, a summary of classification results, a sorted list of detected pathological conditions with their probability scores, and a detailed clinical interpretation with specific insights and recommendations for the significant findings identified (Atelectasis, Cardiomegaly, Pleural Effusion, Pneumonia).
5. The complete report content was then saved to the file 'workspace/report/analysis_report.txt'.
6. The Chest X-ray classification report generation process was completed.
</report>
  <preparation>
1. The dataset was successfully loaded from the specified path: /Users/maksymbidnyi/Downloads/MedDataOS/data/input/24c31571-faaa-4d8f-a1bf-39833b516601_input_dataset.csv.
2. The first 5 rows of the loaded DataFrame, which contained 12 columns, were displayed to show its initial structure.
3. Missing values were checked across all columns, revealing 6 missing values in the 'Subsite' column, representing 6.0% of its data.
4. No numerical columns were found to have missing values, so no imputation with the mean was performed for numerical features.
5. Missing values in the categorical column 'Subsite' were imputed using its mode, which was 'Base of Tongue'.
6. No obvious data type inconsistencies were found or corrected. The data types remained as 'Unnamed: 0' (int64), 'patient_id' (object), 'Age' (float64), 'Sex' (object), 'Smoking PY' (float64), 'Smoking Status' (object), 'Ds Site' (object), 'Subsite' (object), 'T' (object), 'N' (object), 'RADCURE-challenge' (object), and 'ContrastEnhanced' (int64).
7. No duplicate rows were found in the dataset, so none were removed.
8. A new feature named 'Age_Group' was created from the 'Age' column, categorizing ages into groups like 'Child', 'Young Adult', 'Adult', and 'Senior'.
9. The numerical columns 'Unnamed: 0', 'Age', 'Smoking PY', and 'ContrastEnhanced' were normalized using standardization.
10. The categorical columns 'patient_id', 'Sex', 'Smoking Status', 'Ds Site', 'Subsite', 'T', 'N', 'RADCURE-challenge', and 'Age_Group' were one-hot encoded.
11. The information and descriptive statistics of the cleaned and prepared DataFrame were displayed. The final DataFrame contained 100 entries and 163 columns (4 float64, 159 bool).
12. The final cleaned and prepared DataFrame was saved to 'workspace/preparation/output_dataset.csv' as a CSV file without the index.
</preparation>
</shared_knowledge>