<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<shared_knowledge>
  <report_agent>
1. The script initiated the report generation process, internally setting up dummy model performance data that includes classification summaries, model metadata, and overall metrics.
2. The script analyzed the internally provided dummy model execution results by formatting them into a comprehensive text report. This involved creating sections for chest X-ray classification summaries, model information (name, version, training date), and overall performance metrics (accuracy, precision, recall per condition).
3. The script stored the generated report by first ensuring the directory "report_agent" existed, and then writing the complete text report content to the file "report_agent/analysis_report.txt".
4. The report generation process was confirmed as complete.
</report_agent>
  <report>
1. A sample 'results' dictionary, simulating model output for a chest X-ray image (sample_chest_xray_001.jpg) with various pathological condition probabilities, was defined and loaded directly within the script.
2. The script initiated the analysis process, printing a starting message.
3. It defined the report output directory as "workspace/report" and the report file path as "workspace/report/analysis_report.txt".
4. The output directory "workspace/report" was ensured to exist by creating it if it did not already.
5. An analysis report was constructed, including a header, a placeholder for the analysis date (which was N/A as the file didn't exist yet), the analyzed image ID (sample_chest_xray_001.jpg), and a general summary of the chest X-ray classification.
6. The report listed all detected pathological conditions and their probability scores, sorted in descending order of probability.
7. The report identified and highlighted the condition(s) with the highest probability score (Cardiomegaly with a score of 0.8534).
8. The constructed report content was saved to the file "workspace/report/analysis_report.txt".
9. A confirmation message was printed indicating that the report was successfully generated and saved.
</report>
</shared_knowledge>